<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Genç Yazılımcı</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="get_Awards">Get Awards</string>

    <string name="this_awards_delete">prize have been deleted.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="user_nick">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forgot your password?</string>

    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="education_level">Education Level</string>
    <string name="user_name">Name</string>
    <string name="user_surname">Surname</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="google">Google</string>
    <string name="primary_school">Primary School</string>
    <string name="level_29">Level 29</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="information_2">After light is perceived by living things, it is interpreted and made meaningful according to the organs each living thing has and the abilities of these organs. That\'s why, every living things see objects differently.</string>
    <string name="information_1">The first thing required for the act of seeing to occur is light. </string>
    <string name="information_title">How does living things see?</string>
    <string name="alive">Living Thing</string>
    <string name="snake">Snake</string>
    <string name="bee">Bee</string>
    <string name="bat">Bat</string>
    <string name="rabbit">Rabbit</string>
    <string name="computer">Computer ?</string>
    <string name="moveOn">Move On</string>
    <string name="didYouReadInfo">Did you read the info?</string>
    <string name="iRead">Yes, i have read</string>

    <string name="reallyCant">Your really did not see that? \n Look closer…</string>
    <string name="really">Did you really saw there a number 8 :(</string>
    <string name="cant_see">Are you pretty sure to see that?</string>
    <string name="againLook">Since you are so sure.\n Lets look it again :)</string>
    <string name="stillSee">Are you sure you still see the number 8?</string>
    <string name="sureNoSee">Do not worry you still have your coins.\n I was sure that you did not see :)</string>
    <string name="sureSee">Do not worry you still have your coins.\n I was sure that you see that :)</string>
    <string name="absolutelyNot">There certainly are not. \n Or else… maybe we do not see that?</string>
    <string name="closeLook">Lets change the color a little bit.</string>
    <string name="nowSee">Now you can see that a little bit.</string>
    <string name="hardLook">You really did not see that :(</string>
    <string name="hereItIs">Now, it is impossible to not to see</string>
    <string name="congrats">Congratulations.\n Now we are ready for see all of it.</string>
    <string name="stillNo">Can you see that now?</string>
    <string name="hereEight">Here is a number 8.</string>
    <string name="more">You look like ready for more.</string>
    <string name="perfect">Perfect. \n Lets see that better.</string>
    <string name="sure">Are you pretty sure that you did not see? :)</string>
    <string name="machine_how_see">How the machines see?</string>
    <string name="eight_on_the_wall">Our ability to distinguish objects depends entirely on their colour. For example, lets think about a number 8 hanging on the wall.</string>
    <string name="same_color_wall_eight" tools:ignore="Typos">Do you think you can see that if it was the same color as wall?</string>
    <string name="is_there_eight">Is there a number 8 on this wall?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="important_color">As you can see the pictures above, to identify an object, color are very important.</string>
    <string name="machine_equals_string">Each color has a numerical equivalent for machines. The graphic below tells you this simply.</string>
    <string name="question_robot_see">Do you want to learn to how a robot can see?</string>
    <string name="wantTenGoldLose">You look like you want to lose 10 coins.</string>
    <string name="loseTenGold">I am sorry you lost 10 coins.</string>
    <string name="saw">I saw</string>
    <string name="noSaw">I did not see</string>
    <string name="how_robot_does">You did learn how can living things can see. So how can robots distinguish these colors?</string>
    <string name="close_eight">1-) Lets look closer to number 8 that drawn at the first picture on the wall.</string>
    <string name="string_to_hash">2-) We digitized the colors with the information we learned in the second image.</string>
    <string name="machine_look">3-) In the last image, we see what a machine sees by looking at the number 8 on the wall.</string>
    <string name="learn">Lets learn</string>
    <string name="click_look">Please touch the picture to look closer.</string>
    <string name="are_u_sure_exit">Are you sure that you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="againClickExit">Please press again to exit.</string>

    <string name="no_user_data">User data not found.</string>
    <string name="earned_gold">Coins have earned.</string>
    <string name="earn_ten_gold">10 coins have earned.</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="machine_view">Machine View</string>
    <string name="default_coin">10</string>

    <string name="error_occurred">Error Occurred.</string>
    <string name="not_seen">Have not seen</string>
    <string name="not_answered">Have not answered</string>

    <string name="congratulations">Congratulations, you won!</string>
    <string name="press_mine">You stepped on a mine!</string>

    <string name="already_seen">Already Seen</string>
    <string name="already_answered">Already Answered</string>
    <string name="havent_seen">Have not Seen</string>
    <string name="havent_answered">Have not Answered</string>
    <string name="true_answer">True, you can continue!</string>
    <string name="wrong_answer">Wrong answer. Restart the game.</string>
    <string name="answer_one" tools:ignore="Typos">answer1</string>
    <string name="answer_two">answer2</string>
    <string name="answer_three">answer3</string>
    <string name="answer_four">answer4</string>

    <string name="please_answer">Please answer the question.</string>
    <string name="all_question_answered">You answer all the questions correctly. Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="empty" />

    <string name="prize_updated_as">\u0020prize update as\u0020</string>
    <string name="coin_updated_as">\u0020coin</string>
    <string name="prize_has_been_added">\u0020prize has been added</string>
    <string name="new_coin_value">You must enter the new coin value.</string>

    <string name="please_enter_one">Please enter coin for the\u0020</string>
    <string name="please_enter_two">Please enter a gift for\u0020</string>
    <string name="please_enter_award_and_coin">Please enter gift name and gold value first.</string>
    <string name="please_worth_coin_enter_prize">\u0020coin</string>
    <string name="please_prize_for_enter_coin">\u0020prize.</string>

    <string name="please_check_your_email">Please check your email.</string>
    <string name="please_check_your_pass">Please check your password.</string>
    <string name="please_check_your_pass_size">Password should be at least 6 characters</string>

    <string name="please_check_field">Please do not leave any blank field.</string>

    <string name="baseUrl">"https://raw.githubusercontent.com/"</string>

    <string name="your_turn">Your turn!</string>
    <string name="rival_turn">Enemy\'s turn!</string>

    <string name="see_question">See the question</string>

    <string name="third_round_start">Start to third turn</string>

    <string name="zero">0</string>
    <string name="x">X</string>

    <string name="game_win">You won. Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="game_lose">You lost. Please play again!</string>
    <string name="lets_play">Let\'s play!</string>

    <string name="click_question_see">Please press the see the question button.</string>

    <string name="true_answer_two">Right answer! You can continue to play.</string>
    <string name="wrong_answer_two">Wrong answer! Enemy\'s turn.</string>

    <string name="random">random</string>
    <string name="not_random">notRandom</string>

    <string name="nice_answer">Correct answer. Keep continue!</string>
    <string name="please_click_round_button">Please press the start turn button.</string>

    <string name="you_won">Congratulations! You beat your enemy.</string>
    <string name="last_word_press_enter">Please enter a word starting with the last letter of the above expression and press the enter key on the keyboard.</string>
    <string name="machine_learning">Machine Learning</string>
    <string name="machine_learning_information">Machine learning gives a robot the ability to think like a human. But can a robot think completely like a human?</string>
    <string name="machine_human_info_one">Everything we see with our eyes is interpreted by our brain and tried to make it meaningful.</string>
    <string name="machine_human_info_two">The process of making what we see meaningful is learning.</string>
    <string name="machine_human_info_three">Although many sense organs are used for this learning process, we can say that it basically starts with the eye and ends with the brain.</string>
    <string name="machine_human_info_four">Everything we perceive with our sense organs is interpreted by the brain, with the help of nerves located all over our body.</string>
    <string name="machine_human_info_five">So how can machines learn?</string>
    <string name="machine_human_info">The mystery of the human brain has not been solved even today.</string>
    <string name="machine_machine_neural">Can a machine literally learn and think like a human?</string>
    <string name="machine_machine_neural_info_two">The answer to this question should probably be no, while the human brain has not yet fully understood by humanity.</string>
    <string name="machine_machine_info_three">As a result of the developed technologies and many researches, the machines have gained great capabilities. Some of these are as follows:</string>
    <string name="machine_machine_info_four">- Answering the questions \n- Making physically moves\n- Ability to detect objects</string>
    <string name="machine_machine_neural_info_five">We will learn a lot about machines that have many more abilities apart from these mentioned.</string>
    <string name="machine_can_teach_info_one">We learned a little about the human brain and what machines can learn.</string>
    <string name="machine_can_teach_info_two">So, can a machine start teaching people what it has learned?</string>
    <string name="machine_can_teach_info_three">Although machines can gain the ability to learn on their own, they are not comparable to humans.</string>
    <string name="machine_can_teach_info_four">With the development of technology, machines that are constantly developing may be much more advanced than the human brain in the future.</string>
    <string name="machine_can_teach_info_five">The biggest obstacle to achieving this is that the people who will develop these technologies are not working enough in this field.</string>
    <string name="machine_can_teach_info_six">We can accomplish that together.</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="choose_category">- Choose category</string>
    <string name="win_game">- Win the games</string>
    <string name="collect_awards">- Collect the prizes</string>
    <string name="ready_to_fun">- Ready for fun</string>
    <string name="machine_choose_section_info_one">You\'ve learned a lot about humans and robots so far. We can move on to the game world to reinforce these and learn more.</string>
    <string name="game_world">Game World</string>

    <string name="back_main_menu">Do you want to go to Homepage?</string>
    <string name="click_main_menu">Go to Homepage</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="click_image">You can click the image.</string>
    <string name="your">You: </string>
    <string name="retry_game">Restart the game</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="next_question">Next question</string>
    <string name="are_u_sure_quit_game">Do you want to leave the game?</string>

    <string name="ai_game_true">True</string>
    <string name="ai_game_false">False</string>

    <string name="exit">Leave</string>
    <string name="true_ai">True</string>
    <string name="false_ai">False</string>
    <string name="awards_already_collected_ai">The prize have been taken.</string>
    <string name="ai_learning_three">aiLearningThree</string>
    <string name="ai_learning_two">aiLearningTwo</string>
    <string name="ai_learning_one">aiLearningOne</string>
    <string name="click_screen">You can touch the screen for reaching the information</string>

    <string name="game_one">First game</string>
    <string name="game_two">Second game</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>

    <string name="mine_sweeper">Mine Sweeper</string>

    <string name="question">Question: </string>

    <string name="what_is_ai">What is artificial intelligence?</string>
    <string name="is_ai_one">Artificial intelligence is the ability of a computer system to perform tasks often associated with abilities unique to intelligent beings.</string>
    <string name="need_ai">Why do we need the Artificial Intelligence?</string>
    <string name="education_two_info">With the development of today\'s technology, new inventions have emerged. The purpose of these inventions is to make human life easier. The increasing number of inventions that will facilitate human life with artificial intelligence explains why we need artificial intelligence. An example is autonomous vehicles.</string>
    <string name="how_work_ai">How artificial intelligence works?</string>
    <string name="that_work_ai">The working principle of artificial intelligence is to collect a lot of data, create data pools and prepare instructions on what to do by using this data by artificial intelligence. These guidelines are tested millions of times in lifelike simulations. It is developed in a continuous improvement cycle by weeding out faulty instructions and replicating the correct ones. At the end of this process, a faster and more accurate control mechanism is obtained than can be done using ordinary coding techniques. Once a good enough set of instructions is obtained, it can be finalized and tested in the real world.</string>
    <string name="where_use_ai">Where Artificial Intelligence is Used?</string>
    <string name="that_where_work_ai">Artificial intelligence is used in image processing, audio processing, text processing, data processing, decision support systems of autonomous vehicles, virtual assistants, game engines, suggestion systems and similar areas.</string>
    <string name="when_work_ai">When Was the Term Artificial Intelligence First Used?</string>
    <string name="that_when_work_ai">The term "Artificial Intelligence" was first used in 1956 at the "Dartmouth Conference", an artificial intelligence conference.</string>
    <string name="who_use_ai">By Who Was The Term Artificial Intelligence Used?</string>
    <string name="that_who_use_ai">The term “Artificial Intelligence” was first used by Computer Scientist and Cognitive Scientist “John McCarthy”.</string>

    <string name="autonomous_cars">Autonomous Cars</string>
    <string name="education_four_ai_info_one">Autonomous vehicles supported by artificial intelligence and deep learning algorithms are called vehicles that can operate without a driver thanks to their environmental sensing capabilities. This technology, which has already started to be used in daily travels and transportation, gives important clues to the future in the automotive world.</string>
    <string name="education_four_ai_info_two">As a result of the impressions of the above-mentioned visuals, autonomous vehicles can drive safely by distinguishing the objects they see on the road, such as people, and by following the traffic rules.</string>

    <string name="education_one_info_one">Artificial intelligence is the ability of a computer system to mimic human cognitive functions such as learning and problem solving.</string>
    <string name="education_one_info_two">The term artificial intelligence was first coined in 1956 at a conference held at Dartmouth College in New Hampshire, England.</string>
    <string name="education_one_info_three">However, the reason why artificial intelligence is not so popular today is the increasing number of data that can be analyzed in our developing world.</string>
    <string name="education_one_info_four">In addition, the capabilities of artificial intelligence include functions such as understanding human speech, playing games that require counter-move, controlling devices that require autonomous operation, data analysis, military simulation, and photo-video analysis.</string>

    <string name="education_three_info">Artificial Neural Network</string>
    <string name="education_three_info_one">Artificial Neural Networks are parallel and distributed information processing structures, inspired by the human brain, connected to each other through weighted connections and consisting of processing elements, each of which has its own memory.</string>
    <string name="education_three_info_two">Let\'s Take A Look At The Neural Network Model</string>
    <string name="education_three_info_three">Let\'s Take A Look At A Real Neural Network</string>
    <string name="education_three_info_four">As we can see in the images, the way the artificial neural network and the simple biological nervous system work is very similar. In other words, it is the digital modeling of biological neuron cells and the synaptic bond that these cells establish with each other.</string>

    <string name="education_four_info">Uses of Artificial Intelligence Autonomous Vehicles</string>
    <string name="education_four_info_one">Let\'s See the Difference of Artificial Intelligence</string>
    <string name="done_education_four">You Have Successfully Completed the Artificial Intelligence Basic Level Training</string>

    <string name="basic_ai">Artificial Intelligence Fundamentals</string>

    <string name="classification">Classification</string>
    <string name="clustering">Clustering</string>
    <string name="algorithm">Algorithm</string>

    <string name="education_threetwo_info_one">In classification, a dataset is assigned to one of the different and predetermined classes. Classification algorithms are based on learning which data to assign to which class from the given training set.</string>
    <string name="education_threetwo_info_two">Clustering is the grouping of data showing similar characteristics in a data set. Within the same cluster, the similarities are high, and the similarities between the clusters are low. </string>
    <string name="education_three_two_info_three">It is the logical, sequential expression of all the operations needed to solve a problem. The concept of algorithm can be used in programming or software development, as well as activities in daily life, mathematics, etc. It provides the opportunity to solve the problems encountered in the lessons more easily.</string>

    <string name="not_enough_money">You don\'t have enough gold. You can keep learning to earn gold.</string>

    <string name="done_introduction_ai_lesson">You Have Successfully Completed the Introduction to Artificial Intelligence Training</string>
    <string name="get_awards_and_back_main">Get your reward and return to the Homepage</string>

    <string name="back_to_education_ai">Get your reward and return to the Homepage</string>

    <string name="ai">Artificial Intelligence</string>
    <string name="fiveNoneK">5 Ws</string>
    <string name="games">Games</string>
    <string name="ai_with_fiveNoneK">Artificial Intelligence with 5 Ws</string>
    <string name="done_ai_with_fiveNoneK">You Have Successfully Completed Your Artificial Intelligence 5 Ws Training</string>

    <string name="main_education_info_one">In this section, you will be able to get detailed information about artificial intelligence.</string>

    <string name="question_one">Question 1</string>
    <string name="introduction_ai">Introduction to Artificial Intelligence</string>
    <string name="example_question">There is hardly anyone who is not warned by the elderly to drink warm water after eating ice cream. So what\'s the reason for this? Is it really healthy or is it a bullshit?</string>

    <string name="email_or_password_empty">Email or password is empty.</string>

    <string-array name="education_level">
        <item>pre-school education</item>
        <item>Primary School</item>
        <item>Middle School</item>
        <item>High School</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="word_array">
        <item>machine</item>
        <item>artificial intelligence</item>
        <item>machine learning</item>
        <item>artificial intelligence networks</item>
        <item>computer</item>
        <item>processing power</item>
        <item>Database</item>
        <item>data mining</item>
        <item>supervised learning</item>
        <item>unsupervised learning</item>
        <item>bayes</item>
        <item>fuzzy logic</item>
        <item>pattern recognition</item>
        <item>inductive logic programming</item>
        <item>deep learning</item>
        <item>neural networks</item>
        <item>data science</item>
        <item>big data</item>
        <item>cloud technology</item>
        <item>robot</item>
        <item>reinforcement learning</item>
        <item>edison</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="firebase_userData">UserData</string>
    <string name="firebase_userName">userName</string>
    <string name="firebase_userSurname">userSurname</string>
    <string name="firebase_userEmail">userEmail</string>
    <string name="firebase_userNick">userNick</string>
    <string name="firebase_educationLevel">userEducationLevel</string>
    <string name="firebase_userBirthday">userBirthday</string>
    <string name="firebase_aiLearningOne">aiLearningOne</string>
    <string name="firebase_aiLearningTwo">aiLearningTwo</string>
    <string name="firebase_aiLearningThree">aiLearningThree</string>
    <string name="firebase_userCoin">userCoin</string>
    <string name="firebase_userMoney">userMoney</string>
    <string name="firebase_firstCoin">firstCoin</string>
    <string name="firebase_secondCoin">secondCoin</string>
    <string name="firebase_thirdCoin">thirdCoin</string>
    <string name="firebase_fourthCoin">fourthCoin</string>
    <string name="firebase_fifthCoin">fifthCoin</string>
    <string name="firebase_sixthCoin">sixthCoin</string>

    <string name="image_small">image_small</string>
    <string name="image_small2">image_small2</string>
    <string name="image_small3">image_small3</string>
    <string name="image_big">image_big</string>
    <string name="image_big2">image_big2</string>
    <string name="image_big3">image_big3</string>

    <string name="anim_image_big">anim_image_big</string>
    <string name="anim_image_big2">anim_image_big2</string>
    <string name="anim_image_big3">anim_image_big3</string>
    <string name="anim_image_big4">anim_image_big4</string>
    <string name="anim_image_big5">anim_image_big5</string>
    <string name="anim_image_big6">anim_image_big6</string>
    <string name="award">Award</string>

    <string name="hash_award">award</string>
    <string name="hash_coin">coin</string>

    <string name="firebase_mail_error">The email address is badly formatted.</string>
    <string name="firebase_pass_error">The password is invalid or the user does not have a password.</string>
    <string name="firebase_sign_up_pass_error">The given password is invalid. [ Password should be at least 6 characters ]</string>

</resources>